Finding Aid for Michigan State Grange Records, 1873-2005
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Photographs
  - Earlier photos, pre-1930, 1 folder
    - Charlotte Grange members appearing in pageant in Grand Rapids circa 1905 (Box 54)
    - Group portrait of women in auditorium circa 1920s (Box 54)
    - Allegan Grange officers 1920s (Box 54)
    - Eaton County Pomona 1920s (Box 54)
  - Later photographs mainly from the 1940s, 1950s
    (folder description)
    - Danby Grange, Ionia County. Stage performance including use of blackface actors (Box 54)
    - Exhibits and displays (Box 54)
    - Farm equipment and activities (Box 54)
    - Foreign visitors (Box 54)
    - Grange buildings and other landmarks (Box 54)
    - Group photos (many identified) 1950s, undated, 2 folders (Box 54)
    - Hot air balloon (Box 54)
    - Ludington, Michigan Grange members 1953-1956 (Box 54)
    - Michigan Governors (group photos)
      - Lurin D. Dickinson (Box 54)
      - William Milliken (Box 54)
      - George Romney (Box 54)
      - John B. Swainson (Box 54)
      - G. Mennen Williams (Box 54)
    - Michigan Legislators and other officials (Box 54)
    - Mystery ride, Isabella County July 1952 (Box 54)
    - People eating (Box 54)
    - State Grange conventions
      - Muskegon 1950 (Box 54)
      - Cadillac 1951 (Box 54)
      - Grand Rapids 1953 (Box 54)
      - Cadillac 1958 (Box 54)
    - State Grange Petoskey 1956 (Box 54)
    - Youth conference and youth activities (Box 54)
  - Later photographs mainly from the 1950s (Box 55)
    (unprocessed; most of the photos have curled with age and are difficult to examine; representative images will be found in box 54)
  - Later photographs mainly from the 1950s (Box 56)
Below are two indices to the records of the defunct Grange chapters. One of these is arranged alphabetically by the name of the Grange chapter. The second index is arranged by the number given to the Grange chapter. The index refers to the box number where records have been located.
Index to Chapter Records Arranged by Chapter Name
Adrian Grange #213 (Lenawee County)
Boxes 13-14
Alba Bramble Grange #1801
Box 22
Ann Arbor Grange #1566 (Washtenaw County)
Box 34
Antrim County Pomona Grange #38
Box 18
Ash Center Grange #471 (Monroe County)
Box 33
Austin Grange #1331 (Hillsdale County)
Boxes 49-50
Bay Grange #597 (Arenac County)
Box 22
Bear Creek Grange #1266 (Emmet County)
Box 37
Belleville Grange #331 (Wayne County)
Box 22
Bennington Grange #873 (Shiawassee County)
Box 27
Birthday Grange #1352 (Schoolcraft County)
Box 34
Boise Grange #1181 (Midland County)
Box 25
Bruce Armada Grange #657 (Macomb County)
Box 17
Burton Center Grange #1072 (Genesee County)
Box 31
Cambria Grange #74 (Hillsdale County)
Box 30
Coleman Grange #1226 (Midland County)
Box 29
Crawford Grange #934 (Crawford County)
Box 27
Cusic Lake Grange #1728 (Macomb County)
Box 22
Davis Grange #1199 (Macomb County)
Box 22
Davison Grange #1285 (Genesee County)
Box 31
Devereaux Grange #45 (Jackson County) (formerly Springport Grange)
Boxes 32-33
Donaldson-Rosedale Grange #1160 (Chippewa County)
Box 19
East Almer Grange #1701 (Tuscola County)
Box 34
Ellington Grange #1650 (Tuscola County)
Box 34
Elmira Grange #1863 (Antrim County)
Box 18
Faith Grange #594 (Sanilac County)
Box 34
Fenton Grange #1839 (Genesee County)
Box 12
Fisher Grange #790 (Alcona County)
Box 10
Forest Grange #823 (Saginaw County)
Box 26 and 45
Forest Lawn Grange #1720 (Tuscola County)
Box 33
Four Towns Grange #745 (Lenawee County)
Box 27
Fruit Ridge Grange #276 (Lenawee County)
Box 27
Gaines Grange (Genesee County)
Box 17
Genesee Pomona Grange #48
Box 11
Geneva Grange #1227 (Midland County)
Box 27
Goodrich Grange #887 (Genesee County)
Box 30
Grant-Eckland Grange #1724 (Tuscola County)
Box 34
Grass Lake Grange #925 (Antrim County)
Box 23
Harbor Springs Grange #730 (Emmet County)
Box 31
Hayes Grange #871(Otsego County)
Boxes 51-52
Iosco County Pomona #89
Box 34
Ironwood Grange #1800 (Gogebic County)
Box 30
Jackson County Pomona Grange #79
Box 18
Lafayette Grange #92 (Washtenaw County)
Box 35
Lakefield Grange #1764 (Saginaw County)
Box 34
Lakeview Juvenile Grange #148 (Otsego County)
Box 33
Lapeer Grange #246
Box 30
Lickly Corners Grange #274 (Ransom Township, Hillsdale County)
Boxes 15-16
Little River Grange #1855 (Menominee County)
Box 8
Macomb County Pomona Grange #32
Box 27
Maple Grove Grange #1255 (Charlevoix County)
Box 28
Maple Hill Grange #691 (Antrim County)
Box 27
Maple River Grange #1437 (Emmet County)
Box 24
Marion Center #956 (Charlevoix County)
Box 28
Marquette County Pomona Grange #77
Box 33
Medina Grange #277 (Lenawee County)
Box 28
Millington Grange #755 (Tuscola County)
Box 30
North Rome Grange #735 (Lenawee County)
Box 10
North Sylvan Grange #1460 (Washtenaw County)
Box 31
Onsted Grange #279 (Lenawee County) (formerly Springville Grange)
Boxes 6-7
Pioneer Grange #811 (Oscoda County)
Box 5
Pittsfield Union Grange #882 (Washtenaw County)
Boxes 38-39
Ponto Grange #1262 (Saginaw County)
Box 30
Resort Grange #841 (Emmet County)
Box 35
Riverside Grange #741 (Cheboygan County)
Box 19
Rock Elm Grange #705 (Charlevoix County)
Box 29
Rollin Grange #1814 (Manitou Beach, Lenawee County)
Box 9
Rose Township Grange #1826 (Oakland County)
Box 31
Rudyard Grange #1824 (Chippewa County)
Box 19
Saginaw Grange #770
Box 34
Saline Grange #1831 (Washtenaw County)
Box 27
Scio Grange #329 (Washtenaw County)
Box 40
Skandia Grange #1410 (Marquette County)
Box 27
South Arm Grange #815 (Charlevoix County)
Box 27
South Dover Grange #720 (Lenawee County)
Box 27
Studley Junior Grange #321 (Midland County)
Box 34
Tipton Grange #165 (Lenawee County)
Boxes 3-4
Twin Lakes Grange #1811 (Montmorency County)
Box 19
Unionville Grange #1636 (Tuscola County)
Box 30
Washtenaw-Wayne Pomona Grange #7
Box 41
Webster Grange #1111 (Washtenaw County)
Box 39
Weston Grange #276 (Lenawee County)
Box 27
Wheatland Grange #273 (Hillsdale County)
Boxes 20-21
Woodstock Grange #438 (Lenawee County)
Box 27
Index to Chapter Records (arranged by number)
Washtenaw-Wayne Pomona Grange #7
Box 41
Macomb County Pomona Grange #32
Box 27
Antrim County Pomona Grange #38
Box 18
Devereaux Grange #45 (Jackson County) (formerly Springport Grange)
Boxes 32-33
Genesee Pomona Grange #48
Box 11
Cambria Grange #74 (Hillsdale County)
Box 30
Marquette County Pomona Grange #77
Box 33
Jackson County Pomona Grange #79
Box 18
Iosco County Pomona #89
Box 34
Lafayette Grange #92 (Washtenaw County)
Box 35
Lakeview Juvenile Grange #148 (Otsego County)
Box 33
Tipton Grange #165 (Lenawee County)
Boxes 3-4
Adrian Grange #213 (Lenawee County)
Boxes 13-14
Lapeer Grange #246
Box 30
Wheatland Grange #273 (Hillsdale County)
Boxes 20-21
Lickly Corners Grange #274 (Ransom Township, Hillsdale County)
Boxes 15-16
Fruit Ridge Grange #276 (Lenawee County)
Box 27
Weston Grange #276 (Lenawee County)
Box 27
Medina Grange #277 (Lenawee County)
Box 28
Onsted Grange #279 (Lenawee County)(formerly Springville Grange)
Boxes 6-7
Studley Junior Grange #321 (Midland County)
Box 34
Scio Grange #329 (Washtenaw County)
Box 40
Belleville Grange #331 (Wayne County)
Box 22
Woodstock Grange #438 (Lenawee County)
Box 27
Ash Center Grange #471 (Monroe County)
Box 33
Faith Grange #594 (Sanilac County)
Box 34
Bay Grange #597 (Arenac County)
Box 22
Bruce Armada Grange #657 (Macomb County)
Box 17
Maple Hill Grange #691 (Antrim County)
Box 27
Rock Elm Grange #705 (Charlevoix County)
Box 29
South Dover Grange #720 (Lenawee County)
Box 27
Harbor Springs Grange #730 (Emmet County
Box 31
North Rome Grange #735 (Lenawee County)
Box 10
Riverside Grange #741 (Cheboygan County)
Box 19
Four Towns Grange #745 (Lenawee County)
Box 27
Millington Grange #755 (Tuscola County)
Box 30
Saginaw Grange #770
Box 34
Fisher Grange #790 (Alcona County)
Box 10
Pioneer Grange #811 (Oscoda County)
Box 5
South Arm Grange #815 (Charlevoix County)
Box 27
Forest Grange #823 (Saginaw County)
Box 26 and 45
Resort Grange #841 (Emmet County)
Box 35
Hayes Grange #871 (Otsego County
Boxes 51-52
Lakeview Grange #872 (Otsego County)
Box 31
Bennington Grange #873 (Shiawassee County)
Box 27
Pittsfield Union Grange #882 (Washtenaw County)
Boxes 38-39
Goodrich Grange #887 (Genesee County)
Box 30
Grass Lake Grange #925 (Antrim County)
Box 23
Crawford Grange #934 (Crawford County)
Box 27
Marion Center #956 (Charlevoix County)
Box 28
Burton Center Grange #1072 (Genesee County)
Box 31
Webster Grange #1111 (Washtenaw County)
Box 39
Donaldson-Rosedale Grange #1160 (Chippewa County)
Box 19
Boise Grange #1181 (Midland County)
Box 25
Davis Grange #1199 (Macomb County)
Box 22
Coleman Grange #1226 (Midland County)
Box 29
Geneva Grange #1227 (Midland County)
Box 27
Maple Grove Grange #1255 (Charlevoix County)
Box 28
Ponto Grange #1262 (Saginaw County)
Box 30
Bear Creek Grange #1266 (Emmet County)
Box 37
Davison Grange #1285 (Genesee County)
Box 31
Austin Grange #1331 (Hillsdale County
Boxes 49-50
Birthday Grange #1352 (Schoolcraft County)
Box 34
Skandia Grange #1410 (Marquette County)
Box 27
Maple River Grange #1437 (Emmet County)
Box 24
North Sylvan Grange #1460 (Washtenaw County)
Box 31
Ann Arbor Grange #1566 (Washtenaw County)
Box 34
Unionville Grange #1636 (Tuscola County)
Box 30
Ellington Grange #1650 (Tuscola County)
Box 34
East Almer Grange #1701 (Tuscola County)
Box 34
Forest Lawn Grange #1720 (Tuscola County)
Box 33
Grant-Eckland Grange #1724 (Tuscola County)
Box 34
Cusic Lake Grange #1728 (Macomb County)
Box 22
Lakefield Grange #1764 (Saginaw County)
Box 34
Ironwood Grange #1800 (Gogebic County)
Box 30
Alba Bramble Grange #1801
Box 22
Twin Lakes Grange #1811 (Montmorency County)
Box 19
Rollin Grange #1814 (Manitou Beach, Lenawee County)
Box 9
Rudyard Grange #1824 (Chippewa County)
Box 19
Saline Grange #1831 (Washtenaw County)
Box 27
Fenton Grange #1839 (Genesee County)
Box 12
Little River Grange #1855 (Menominee County)
Box 8
Elmira Grange #1863 (Antrim County)
Box 18
Gaines Grange (Genesee County
Box 17